Guide to the Ipas Records, 1965-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Africa Programs, 1973-2004, (18 boxes)
  - South Africa Programs 1994-2002: Women's health projects 94-00; DFID history 95-99; new ideas 95-97; correspondence 95-01; ODA project 96-98; RRA Alliance 96-00; curriculum 97; midwives (Box 45)
  - Kenya Programs 1986-1997: trip reports 87-92; correspondence 86-88; Kenya II proposal/contracts 88-90; correspondence 89-91; donor correspondence 94; reports 94-95; background 95-99; country summaries 95-99; Clinical Officers project working files 96-97; REACH numbers 96-98; Nairobi office 97-01; FCI 97; Kenya OR (operations research) working files 95-98; National Expansion working files 96-98; Sida projects 97 (Box 46)
  - Kenya Programs 1998-1999: OR dissemination 98; background 98-00; refugee project working files 98-99; PRIME I working files 98-00; Khama Rogo 99; Sida proposal and contracts 99-01; Kenya donor proposals 99-00 (Box 47)
  - Kenya Programs 2000-2004: ICR handover 00; PAC scale-up mtg 00; CHAK 00; Orero 00; COBAC paper 00; PRIME I dissemination 00; PRIME II working files 00-02; Women's Health Project 00; WHO safe ab mtg 00; Pathfinder USAID project proposal/working files 00-01; correspondence 00-01; Ipas/FIDA/KMA proposal 00-01; minutes 00-01; WHO midwifery module 00-01; reports 00-02; trip reports 00-03; strategic plan 01-05; Sida/AVSC proposal/planning 01; Sida reports 01; Teen Web survey proposal 01; RHAP project 01; small grants proposal 01-02; K2 launch 01-03; planning 02; donor profiles 02; research data 02-03; TeenWeb project and dissemination 02-03; hand-off to Alliance 03; planning 03 (Box 48)
  - Ethiopia Programs 1988-2000: background 88-93; comms 91-93; Ethiopia II donor proposal/reports 92-96; history of programs 92-99; background 93-98; MOH agreements 95-96; Ethiopia II working files 94-95; working files 96-97; correspondence and reports 96-97; proposals 96-98; talks/papers 96-99; background 98-99; reports 98-00; donor proposals/reports 98-01; correspondence 98-01; ESOG 99-00; NGO registration 00; small grants 99-00; RH mtg 00; TOTs 00; workplan/logframe 00-01; team minutes 00-01; trip reports 00-02; small grants 00-02; donor reports 00-03; progress reports 00-03; donor proposals/correspondence 5 year project 00-03; country 00-04 (Box 49)
  - Ethiopia Programs 2001-2004: consultants 01, legal reform 01, monthly reports 01; office lease 01-02; workplans 01-02; small grants program 01-02; Saba visit 02; Hailu orientation 02; HAPSCO presentation 02; CPRHA curriculum 02; management/monitoring 01-03; BOD presentation 02; 63iii 02; pre-service curriculum 02-03; RAMOS proposal 03; program overview/planning 03; Finland proposal 03; internal report 03; AWG 03; small grants 03; donor report 03-04; planning 04; management/monitoring 04; Netherlands contract 04; donor workplan year 4 04-05 (Box 50)
  - Ghana Programs 1989-2004: proposals 92; clinic project 82-83; equipment 88-97; correspondence 88-97; background/project development 89-95; field proposals/reports 89-96; Kumasi/KATH correspondence 9-94; Korle Bu correspondence 91-96; trip reports 91-93; planning materials 92-95; donor proposals/reports; 93-96; contracts 94; trip reports 94-95; Safe Motherhood 94-96; Brookman Amissah ICR contract/reports 94-96; Ghana II working files 94-95; ICR correspondence 94-96; PRIME 96; Taylor 96-97; working files 96-97; mothercare 96-98; trip reports 96-99; country summary 97-98; workplan 99-00; Taylor at SA conference 99; PRIME 99-00; strategy mtg 00; strategy plan 01-05; Ab care services mtg 04 (Box 51)
  - Uganda Programs 1994-2000: Comms 92-96; trip reports 94-00; WHO 95-96; donor proposals/reports 95-98; program history 95-00; background 95-01; Achurobwe ICR 96; contracts 96; field proposals/reports 96-00; Achurobwe 97-98; comms 97-98; PRIME working files 97-99; midwives study 97; ODA concept paper 98; papers 98-99; comms 99-01; Rose Nalwadda ICR 00; quality of care mtg 00; EDF microprojects 00; Pathfinder collaboration 00; private sector training 00; RH stakeholders 00; DISH working files 00-01; CARE 00-01; team mtg notes 00-01; country plan 00-04 (Box 52)
  - Uganda Programs 2001-2002 and Tanzania Programs 1994-2001: Uganda: GTZ proposal 01, NGO reg, TOT, UPMA proposal, planning 02 Tanzania: Background 90-00, assessment/eval tools workshop 94, country summaries, correspondence. 95-00, Tanz III 95-97 working files, AVSC/Ipas collaboration and assessment tools 95-98, Field reports 97, AVSC/Ipas meetings 97-00, Dr. Urassa 97-99, URT PAC eval 98, AVSC/Ipas 98-00 working files; AVSC/Ipas APHA paper; AVSC subagreement 99; National expansion program working files 99; MOH 00; PRIME 01 (Box 53)
  - Africa Regional files 1989-1997: Lilliane Toumi 83-96; Blumenthal 89-90; Jan Bradley correspondence 89-90; Conference on Adolescent Health 92; Francophone 92; private mission hospitals 92; college of surgeons mtg 92; MWIA congress 93; training numbers 93-95; Lisa Bohmer regional rep 94; regional trainers workshop 94; African Medical Association Conference 94-95; E&S Africa PAC proposal 94-96; ministers mtg 95; regional RH workshop 95; PAFP TOT 95; Bohmer correspondence 95-96; regional correspondence 95-99; advocacy Rogo 96; E&S Africa project working files 95-97; Policy Project 96-97; Aloo-Obunga reg rep 96-98; standards correspondence 96-98; UNFPA/CEDPA adolescent mtg 97; E&S Africa strat mtg 97; CMA 97; PRIME ECSACON 97; E&S Africa working files 97-99; policy project 97-98; CAMAS 97-98; ECSCOGS 97-99 (Box 54)
  - Africa Regional files 1998-2004: Nairobi regional office 98; E&S Africa Standards document 98; E&S Africa donor correspondence; PRIME 99; Partnership ideas 99; internal reports 99; Khama Rogo - medical advisor 99-01; Africa strategy planning meeting 00; objectives/progress 00; fundraising 00-03; Pop Council mtg 01; planning 01; cluster mtg minutes 02; planning 02; planning 03; planning documents 03; Addis regional unsafe abortion mtg 03; post-Addis follow-up 03; policy planning 04; Sida proposal 04-07 (Box 55)
  - Africa: Miscellaneous countries 1987-2002: Botswana correspondence 91-97, PAC training 01, MVA workshop 02; Cameroon 99; Egypt 02; Lesotho 96; Malawi working files 94-96; Swaziland 01; Zaire trip reports 87-91, Pop Council correspondence 89-90, correspondence 90, correspondence Martin 90-91, proposal/reports 90-91, general correspondence 89-90; Zambia trip reports 87-92, donor proposals/report 91-93, correspondence 93-96, reports 94-95, Zimbabwe donor proposal 95-96, correspondence 96, country summaries 95-99, trip reports 89-92, correspondence 89-93, research project 90-91, contract 91, TOT 91, field reports 90-92, blocked funds 93-95, UNFPA 96, TOT 96, ZNFPC 96-98, trip reports 96-97; planning 96-98; background 96-01 (Box 56)
  - Africa Alliance 2000-2003: AA structure planning 00-01; office team minutes 00-03; research 01-02; donor proposals/reports 00-02; internal reports 01-03; small grants 01-03; Africa Ipas map 02; planning/objectives 02; presentation to Ipas BOD 02; fundraising 02-03; trip reports 02-03; donor World Bank 02-03; Euro donor 02-03; Kenya baseline study 03; Mozambique 02-03; training reports/schedules 03; regional summaries 02-03; CMHW curriculum 03; Kenya maendelo project 03; Addis meeting 03; Addis mtg statements 03; donor proposals/reports 02-05; Workplans 03; Brookman-Amissah visit NC 03; donor visits 03; Dr. Mwalili 03; Braam 03; Zimbabwe 03; Kenya planning 03; AA relocation issues 03; 63iii 03; program reviews 03; comms 03; planning/budgets 03; Kenya abortion debate 04; planning/monitoring 04; donor JICA 04; Tanzania 04; Namibia 04; Kenya 04; Kenya TeenWeb lessons 04; diagram structure 04; internal reports 04; CIDA magnitude study 04 (Box 57)
  - Africa (miscellaneous files) 1987-2003: Africa Mission Trip report 1987, Africa regional trainers mtg 94, MWIA conference 94, regional docs 00-03, Ethiopia posters, Ghana misc 94-95, Ghana strategy mtg 01, Ghana "Linking Research to Action" mtg 01, Ghana CAC assessment 05, Kenya funders 90-91, Kenya MVA Eval 92, Kenya donor reports 92-95, Malawi corresp 00, Nigeria donor reports 81-93, Nigeria donor proposals/reports 81-93, Nigeria MVA training 90-91, Nigeria Brookman-Amissah reception 02, Tanzania misc 94-96, Zaire 87-91, Zambia donor reports 90-92, Zambia field reports 91, Zimbabwe MVA trainings 91-94, South Africa misc 01-02 (Box 108)
- Chronological Files, 1974-2004, (7 boxes)
  - 1974 (June-December), 1975, 1976 (missing June), 1977-1979 (Box 58)
  - 1980, 1982, 1984 (January-June), 1985 (March-April), 1986 (July, September, October), 1987 (March-November), 1988 (May, October, November), 1989 (January, April, May, September-December), 1990 (Box 59)
  - 1991-1993, 1994 (January-June) (Box 60)
  - 1995-1996, 1997 (January-June) (Box 61)
  - 1997 (July-December), 1998-2000, 2001 (January-May) (Box 62)
  - 2001 (June-November), 2002-2003, 2004 (January-June) (Box 63)
  - Chrono: July 2004 - March 2006 (each month) (Box 107)
- Program Files and Internal Documentation, 1970-2006, (15 boxes)
  - Ipas Resource Center Archives: APLIC Resources, Pre-Ipas abortion study 1970, Correspondence, database keyword list, user services, library scimate, Popline, APLIC notebook, SECS document collection notebook; database CDs (Box 64)
  - Ipas Internal Trainings and Workshops 1991-2002: Ipas Public Speaking Workshop 1991, Strategic Planning Notebook 1997-1998, Adolescent Teen Pregnancy -- fact sheets, article, and PP presentation 1997-2000, Challenging the Conventional Wisdom: Lessons Learned from Postabortion Family Planning Research 1999, Ipas Matrix Management 1999, Consensus Decision-Making Workshop 2001, Country Team Leader: Training Workshop 2000, "It's OK to Disagree!" Conflict Management Workshop 2000; Reproductive Health for Refugees 2000, Microsoft Outlook Workshops 2001, Réunion Regional de América Latina y el Caribe 2001, Building Capacity for Training Launch and Scale-up: A Workshop for Staff and Lead Trainers 2002, Country Team Leaders' Meeting: "Working and Learning Together" 2002, From Planning to Printing: A Guide to Ipas Publications 2002, Global Event Monitoring System training 2002 (Box 69)
  - Ipas Internal Trainings and Workshops 2003-2004: Fundraising at Ipas 2003, Ipas Program Management Initiative 2003, Common Sense Rules for Workplace Behavior, Level One Leadership Training Series 2004 (Box 70)
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas sponsored-conferences for external audiences: World Federation: Women's Issues Planning Group, Ankara, Turkey, 16-18 Apr 1986; Planned Parenthood Federation of America: Annual Meeting, Boston, MA, 19-22 Nov. 1987; Reproductive Health Technologies Meeting, Reproductive Health Technologies Project, Washington, D.C., 9-May-89; Meeting Women's Needs for Post-Abortion Family Planning, Bellagio, Italy, 1-5 Feb. 1993; NGO Forum, The Population Institute, Cairo, Egypt 5-13 Sep. 1994; Informe de la Conferencia Internacional sobre la Poblacion y el Desarrollo, UN, Cairo, Egypt, 5-13 Sep. 1994; FIGO Montréal 1994, Montreal, Canada, 24-30 Sep. 1994; Inter-Agency Symposium on Reproductive Health in Refugee Situations, UNHCR, UNFPA, UNICEF, WHO, Geneva, Switz. 28-30 Jun. 1995; How and When: A Medical Abortion Update, Preparing Your Clinic for Medical Abortion, National Abortion Federation, Washington, D.C., 31 Mar. 1996; National Council for International Health, Arlington, VA, 25-27 Jun. 1998; Technical Update on Gender-Based Violence and Reproductive Health/HIV, IGWG, Oct-99; High-level Intergovernmental Meeting to Review Regional Implementation of the Beijing Platform for Action, Economic and Social Commission for Asia and the Pacific, Bangkok, Thailand, 26-29 Oct. 1999; Cuba Congress, ALAMES, Cuba, 3-4 Jul. 2000; Choices for Women with Unplanned Pregnancies, Division of Family Planning and Population, Bangkok, Thailand, 6 Jul. 2000; FIGO 2000, Washington, D.C., 3-8 Sep. 2000; Meeting on Maternal Mortality Surveillance, PAHO, Washington, D.C., 16-17 Oct. 2000; Reunion sobre la Vigilancia Epidepmiologica de la Mortalidad Materna, WHO, PAHO, Washington, D.C., 16-17 Oct. 2000, Workshop on Maternal Mortality Epidemiological Surveillance, WHO, PAHO, Washington, D.C., 16-17 Oct. 2000; Conferencia Regional Sobre Programas de Atencion Post-Aborto en América Latina Ministerio de Salud Publica y Aisstencia Social, Guatemala City,21-22 Jun. 2001; Unwanted Pregnancy and Abortion: Public Health Challenges in Latin America and the Caribbean, Instituto Nacional de Salud Publica, Cuernavaca, Mexico, 12-14 Nov. 2001; 45th All India Congress of Obstretics and Gynaecology, FOGSI, Bhubaneswar, India, 6-9 Jan. 2002; Mujeres, Violencia y Salud, Ipas, SSA, Mexico City, MX, 8-12 Apr. 2002; Photos, National Conference and 29th Annual General Meeting of the OBGYN Society of Bangladesh, Bangladesh, 2002; Action to Reduce Maternal Mortality in Africa, Economic Commission for Africa, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, 5-7 Mar. 2003; Advancing Women's Access to Safe Abortion: An International Strategy Wkshp, Ipas, Chapel Hill, NC, 27-30 Apr. 2004; Advancing Women's Access to Safe Abortion: A Regional Strategy Wkshp, Ipas, Nairobi, Kenya, 28-30 June 2004 (Box 71-73)
  - Vacuum Aspiration literature, 1989 and 2003; Core donor proposals and reports, 1987-2003; Rebecca Cook Program of Research, 1994-1997; Communications Unit, 1989-1998; Reprints of articles by Ipas staff in peer-review journals (Box 84)
  - Medical Abortion (MA): Miso background 1994, Methotrexate 1995, PP medical abortion 1996, Mifepristone slides 1996, MA background 1996-1998, Mifepristone background 1997-2003, RHTP mtg 1998, Miso lit review 2000, Safety and efficacy 2001, RH Alliance Europe 2001, Legality/availability/cost 2001-2002, PATH 2001-2003, MA Table 2002, MA Task Force meetings and planning 2001-2004, Safe Access Mtg 2004 (Box 85)
  - PRIME and PRIME II working files, 1997-2003 (Box 86)
  - PRIME and PRIME II reports, 1995-2001 (Box 87)
  - Global and Cross-Regional Programs and Projects: Infection prevention 1987-1993, Working with women's groups 1990, MVA activities 1991, Harrison McKay's trips 1992, World Health Organization clinical guidelines 1992, Women's Perspectives Task Force 1992, Interconnection newsletter 1992-1996, Estimating MVA instruments, Indicators of institutionalization, Evaluation instruments 1992, Bellagio Conference working files 1993, International Women's Health meeting Uganda 1993, PAFP curriculum 1995-1996, Jose David Ortiz 1996, Prevention of Maternal Mortality conference 1996, Mid-level providers 1993-2002 (including ICM conferences), FCI unsafe abortion guide, Programs planning 1998, PAC-PIP working files 1998, 2nd trimester work 1999, UNFPA refugees 1999-2001, P. Blumenthal's presentation at Agra conference 2000, Adolescents 2001 and 2003, Regional Directors retreat 2002, COBAC 2002, program planning 2003, World Health Organization Strategic Assessment 2004 (Box 94)
  - Media Files 1992-2006: Kenya 92-04, Media training 01, media resources 01, PAC Consortium 01-04, PAC Comms Task Force 01-04, S.A. mid-level mtg 02, Addis Meeting working files 03, Hipnet 03, APHA 03, Feminist Majority Fdn 03, Comms strategy 03, Kenya partnership exchange 03, Panos collaboration 03, Doug Gould 03, Nicaragua 03, video distribution 03, Panos commissioning ltrs 03-04, Portraits piece 03, Ipas messages 04, Nepal 04, Doug Gould 04, IFP presentation 04, APHA 04, Ext Comms strategy 04, March for Women's Lives files 04, Catholics for Free Choice Mex City 04, Kenya 04-05, Kings county 05, MVA launch partner presentation 05, Doug Gould 05, L Maguire Ethiopia 05, Circle of Friendship 05, EC 05, Africa country directors media training 05, Treaty Monitoring committees 05, media planning 05, human rights work 05, El Salvador 05, Charlotte paper op-ed 05, Comms/Dev retreat 06, Doug Gould 06, Board visioning 06, Bolivia 06, Media 06, Ayotte v PP 06, UN Millenium project 06, sex selection abortion 06 (Box 95)
  - Ipas Internal Trainings and Workshops, 2001-2005: Genderized: Ipas' Gender Workshop (n.d.); "It's Okay to Disagree": Ipas Workshop on Managing Conflict 2001; Ipas Monitoring and Evaluation Guide: Ipas Africa Staff Meeting 2001; Workshop on Consensus Decision-Making 2001; Building Capacity for Training Launch and Scale-Up 2002; Effective Training Courses (TOT1) 2002; MVA Training for Miscarriage Management 2003; MVA Plus Global Launch 2004; Ipas Project Management Workshop 2004; Ipas Project Management Workshop: Africa Region 2004; Ipas Taller de Gestion de Proyectos 2004; Intranet training Workshop 2005; Alliance for Justice 2005 (Box 110)
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas sponsored-conferences for external audiences: Antiprogestin Drugs: Ethical, Legal and Medical Issues, Arlington, VA, 6-7 December 1991; Honoring our Commitments, US Implementation of the ICPD, Washington, DC, 21-22 February 1996; 3rd Reproductive Health Priorities conference, Western Cape, South Africa, 19-22 August 1997; Roundtable on Reproductive Rights and Implementation of Reproductive Health Programmes, Kampala, Uganda, 22-25 June 1998; Confounding the Critics: Cairo, 5 years on, Cocoyoc Morelos, Mexico, 15-18 November 1998; International Forum of Parliamentarians on ICPD Review, The Hague, Netherlands, 4-6 February 1999; NGO Forum and Youth Fora ICPD + 5, The Hague, Netherlands, 6-7 February 1999; ICPD+5: Fulfilling the Commitment, The Hague, Netherlands, 8-12 February 1999; APHA Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA 21-25 October 2001; Global Health Council, Annual Conference, Washington DC, 28-31 May 02; Initiative Francophone Régionale: Soins Aprés Avortement, Conférence Régionale, Dakar, Senegal, 4-7 March 2002; Global Health Council, Annual Conference, Washington Dc, 28-31 May 2002; APHA Annual Meeting, Philadelphia, PA, 9-13 November 2002; APHA, Annual Meeting, San Francisco, CA, 16-19 November 2003; XV International AIDS Conference, Bangkok, Thailand, 11-16 July 2004; APHA Annual Meeting, Washington DC, 6-10 November 2004; Second Meeting on Abortion Law Reform Strategy in LAC, Mexico City; 21-22 November 2004; Expanding Capacity for a Safe Abortion Movement at the Highest Level, Circle of Friends Workshop, Nairobi, Kenya, 23-25 February 2005; Global Health Council, Annual Conference, Washington DC, 31 May - 3 June 2005; U.S. Global Engagement on Sexual and Reproductive Health and Rights: Strategic Messaging Meeting, Washington DC, 21 July 2005; Réunion de Expertas sobre Alternativas de Atención en el Sector Salud a Mujeres Sobrevivientes de Violencia Sexual, Washington DC, 2-4 August 2005; 3rd Asia Pacific Conference on Reproductive and Sexual Health, Petaling Jaya, Malaysia, 17-21 November 2005; 3rd reunion sobre las Políticas del Aborto en América Latina, Montevideo, Uruguay, 27-28 November 2005; Dialogue on: Role of National MR Program for the Promotion of Sexual and Reproductive Health and Rights in Bangladesh, Dhaka, Bangladesh, 19 February 2006; Outcomes for Advocacy Workshop, New York City, 5 December 2006 (Box 111-112)
- Executive and Management Files, 1965-2006, (7 boxes)
  - Board of Directors correspondence: Correspondence 1986-1996, Infection control correspondence, 1991-1993, Len Laufe 1989-1993, Don Collins 1988-2003, Rebecca Cook 1995-1998, Louise Tyrer 1990-1997, Pouru Bhiwandiwala 1989-2002, Don Minkler 1989-2001, Alta Charo 1992-1993, Jose Pinotti 1992-1994, Orientation 1993, Marcie Musser 1990-1993, Judy Senderowitz 1990-1994, Davy Chikamata 1988-1998, Aziza Husein 1989-1991, Grace Delano 1992-1993, Lance Bronnenkant 1992-2002, Anne Firth Murray 1994-2001, Nicki Nichols Gamble 1994-2001, Ellen Hardy 1997-2001, Dilys Cossey 1996-2004, Paul Blumenthal 1997-2004, Jane Bertrand 2000-2001, Mahmoud Fathalla 2000-02, Gordon Duncas 2000-2005, Jael Silliman 1995-1999, Mable Biano 2002, Angela Kumara 2002-2003, Abe Nkomo 2002-2003, Fred Nunes 2002 (Box 88)
  - OC repackaging 1965-1974, Paper pill project 1974-1975, Trademark 1974-1976, Dr. Paniker (Malaysia) 1974-1980, Patent 1975-1978, Estillita (Brazil) 1975-1978, Egypt husband pill 1976-1977, Malaysia 1976-1980, Fundraising 1977-1978, Wyeth 1978, Battelle report 1978-1979, Mexico clinics 1979-1981, Sales reports 1980-1982, Mexico University Clinic 1980-1982, APSAM 81, Ann Leonard Thai refugee camp research 1985, Ann Leonard correspondence 1986-1989, General info 1987-1988, By-laws and charter 1987-1993, Policies and resolutions 1988-1990, Duff Gillespie's declaration 1990, Plata correspondence 1990-1991, Contract Package 1990, IPAS Clinic Program Loan Application 1975 (Box 89)
  - FDA labeling 1991, PAFP talk 1991, Abortion in the developing world talk K. McLaurin 1991, Forrest Greenslade notes 1991, Strategic planning 1991-1994, F. Greenslade Europe trip 1992, Norplant meeting 1992, APHA 1992, PAFP working group 1992, Staff meetings 1992, John Dorward 1992-1993, Labeling 1992-1995, PAHO 1992-1996, CFC 1992-1996, F. Greenslades messages to Board 1992-1996, Priorities 1993, RHTP 1993, New Delhi presentation F. Greenslade 1993, RU 486 meeting 1993, World Health Organization medical abortion meeting 1993, Staff meetings 1993, Nice letters 1993, Ann Leonard correspondence and internal memos 1993, Katie McLaurin correspondence and internal memos, Personnel policy review 1993, Fundraising 1993, Internal Correspondence 1993, 20th anniversary 1993, Evaluations 1993, Organization overview 1993, "The Grid" 1993, Ann Leonard talks 1993, General presentations 1993, APLIC meeting 1993, USAID talk 1993, Executive office correspondence 1993-1994, Letters other staff 1993-1994, Internal memos 1993-1994, Other correspondence 1993-1994 (Box 90)
  - CAs meeting 1994, Europe trip 1994, PAFP talk Ann Leonard 1994, RHFP presentation K. McLaurin 1994, Ipas overview for IHCAR K. McLaurin 1994, Ann Leonard correspondence 1994, Senior staff meetings 1994, staff meetings 1994, K. McLaurin correspondence 1994, F. Greenslade correspondence 1994, JHPIEGO letter of understanding 1994, MVA statistics 1994, World Health Organization medical abortion meeting 1994, ICPD 1994, FIGO 1994, F. Greenslade Brazil trip 1994, Strategic planning 1994-1995, Introducing MA technologies 1995, Prep for Beijing 1995, Senior staff meetings 1995, Khama Rogo talk 1995, donor meeting 1995, A. Leonard correspondence 1995, F. Greenslade correspondence 1995 (Box 91)
  - IT 1996, F. Greenslade correspondence 1996, Technology transfer paper 1996, Senior staff meetings 1996, LOGIX Egypt 1996-1998, Pharmatec 1996-1999, Accomplishments 1997, Measuring Our Reach 1997, Strategic planning notebook 1998, IT capacity 1998, Quinacrine 1998, Dialapan 1998, Personnel policies 1998-2000, A. Leonard Correspondence 1998-2000, Liz Maguire correspondence 1999, Matrix materials 1999, ISO 1999, Feedback 1999, Strategic plan and objectives 1999, F. Greenslade departure 1999, Board meeting prep 1999-2001, President announcement 1999, President's fund 1999, Colleague organizations 1999 (Box 92)